rocketr.net 2019-12-03

# All In One Payment Processor - Rocketr.net

**By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.**

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which rocketr.net collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") and Clients (each, a "Client") of the https://rocketr.net website ("rocketr.net"). This privacy policy applies to the Site, any and all products and services offered on rocketr.net. For the purpose of this Site: the "User" shall be any person entered onto the Site, including subscribers to our newsletter, and the "Client" shall be any person who has registered with the Site.

### Personal Identification Information of the Client

We will collect only that personal identification information from Clients that they voluntarily submit to us. When registering with the Site, we will ask the Clients to complete a questionnaire. However, refusal to enter the data will prevent the Client from registration and use of our services. The Client, by filling in the data into the questionnaire, shall automatically grant his/her permission to use this data for the following purposes _**only:**_

  * For the performance of the contract between the Site and the Client - such data shall be kept no longer than 3 years from the last transaction of the Client.
  * For sending newsletters, periodic updates, and other notifications the Client.
  * For sending questionnaires for improvement of the Site.
  * For sending emails with commercial information of the Site, unless the Client refuses such information.

We shall not transfer your personal data for any third parties, except when it is essential for the performance of the agreements between the Site and the Client, between the Client and his/her end-customer, and between the Client and third-party payment processors we use (https://paypal.com, https://coinpayments.com, https://perfectmoney.com, https://stripe.com).  

### Personal identification information of the User

Users may visit our Site anonymously. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities. If a User enters his/her personal information into the Site, he/she automatically grants the right to use this information _only for the purpose it was entered into_ the Site, for example, sending newsletters, downloading free products, etc.

### Information we collect

**Registration:** Your username, password and e-mail address when you sign-up for a rocketr.net account.

**User content:** Texts, photos, vector and other images and similar.

**Paid account:** If you choose to continue service with rocketr.net via a paid account, we may collect the following personal data from you: credit card number, credit card expiration date, and postal code, and keep this information on file in our secure server in order to process your recurring invoices. You may, at your will, also provide your company name, full billing address and phone number. This information is used to verify credit card authenticity, and process payments as per your applicable service agreement.

**Google Analytics:** rocketr.net is using Google Analytics to track standard user data on traffic sources, visitor behavior flow, audience overview. We may use your user ID to track specific behavior, however, it cannot be connected to other data we are collecting about the users.

**Server logs and Cookies:** When you access our services online, our web servers automatically create records of your visit. These records typically include IP-address, access times, the sites linked from, pages visited, the links and features used, the content viewed or requested, browser or application type, and other information of such kind. See also our Information on Cookies usage below.

### Web browser cookies

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

### E-mails

The email address the Users of the Clients provide for order processing, will only be used to send them information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. If the User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.

### How we protect your information

We adopt effective and appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes _**only having obtained your prior permission.**_ We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes of statistics and improvement of our services.

### Third party websites

This Privacy Policy applies for this Site only. Users may find content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our Clients, partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

### Changes to this privacy policy

We have the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users and Clients to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

### Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
